The next Easter card I'm going to show you is a lot of fun and it has a film strip technique.
Here's the card that we are going to be making and doesn't that look like a cute little film strip.
You can use this card again, for any card, any season but we are going to be doing Easter.
So let me get started.
First thing I'm going to do is cut and score my paper.
I need a piece of wild wasabi at five and a half times four and a quarter where I'm going to be scoring.
That's my card base.
And then I need a piece of the black which is going to be the film strip and I'm going to cut that at two and three quarters times five and a half which is the length of the card.
Alright now the next pieces that we are going to be using, I don't need my cutters for, we are going to have fun with punching.
I need three squares of the so saffron.
When ever you are using the punches, the punch always has to be up so you can see where you are punching.
So there is one, two, three for our film strip.
Now I won't cut out the chick punches until I've stamped on them.
It makes it a lot easier for me to see the images where I need them.
So let me go ahead and stamp three chicks.
And I'm just stamping my chicks in black.
And what I want to do, I want to capture him, I got a little smudge so I need to stamp one more time.
What I want to do here is capture him at three different stages.
Where he is just peaking, where he's got the middle of his body and then the top of his body kind of pulling out of the screen.
So by doing that what I'm going to do is use my square, line them up.
The first one I want is just going to be his nose.
I'm going to punch that out. The middle one is going to be his body, I'm going to punch that out.
And the last one is going to be his body but he's going to be kind of leaving the scene.
So I need to get a little bit in here and I'm just going to get the top of my chick.
Sometimes you have to cut your little paper a little bit just to get your puncher and there is my third.
So I have all my punches done and now I can start coloring.